Guide to the Cornell University Olin, Kroch, Uris Libraries' administrative records, 1961-2003.
Cornell University Olin, Kroch, Uris Libraries' administrative records, 1961-2003
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Olin, Kroch, Uris Libraries' administrative records, 1961-2003.
13-1-3356
Cornell University.Library.Olin, Kroch, Uris Libraries.
18 cubic ft.
Correspondence, reports, financial records, photographs, videotapes, and subject files
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, reports, statistics, policies, financial records, photographs, videotapes, and subject files relating to advisory groups, conservation, automation and the general administrative operations of the Olin, Kroch, Uris (OKU) libraries.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, reports, statistics, policies, financial records, photographs, videotapes, and subject files relating to advisory groups, conservation, automation and the general administrative operations of the Olin, Kroch, Uris (OKU) libraries.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Corson, David W.; Cornell University.Library.Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections.; Cornell University.Libraries.
Subjects:
Academic libraries--Administration.; Academic libraries--Statistics.; Library administration.; Library architecture.; Library buildings.; Library finance.; Academic librarians.
Form and Genre Terms:
Videotapes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the office of origin.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
The collection retains its original arrangement.
SERIES LIST
Series I: Administrative Operations:
Series II: Administrative Reports
Series III: Advisory Groups
Series IV: Affiliated Programs
Series V: Automation
Series VI: Collections
Series VII: Conservation
Series VIII: Correspondence
Series IX. Departmental Administration
Series X. Development and Public Affairs
Series XI: Finances and Accounting
Series XII: Libraries (CUL) - General
Series XIII: Patron Services
Series XIV: Personnel
Series XV. Physical Plant
Series XVI: Planning
Series XVII: Publications
Series XVIII: Security and Safety
Series XIX: Statistics and General Data
Series XX: Technical Processing
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I: Administrative Operations:
  - 2A. Access/Circulation
    - 2.A.5 Circulation Statistics, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 2.A.10 Library Hours, 1961-2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 2.A.15 Lockers--Kroch, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 2.A.20 User Charges, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 2.A.25 User Charges, 1984-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 2B. Building Access
    - 2.B.10 Alarm Reports, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 2.B.15 Keying Olin, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 2.B.20 Keys--Forms and Policies, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 2.B.25 Strange Occurrences--OKU, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 2F. Miscellaneous Administration
    - 2.F.5 Admin. Ops--General, 1988-1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 2.F.10 Job Descriptions/Classifications, 1986-2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 2.F.15 Plant Care, 1990 & 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 2.F.20 Security Gates, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 2.F.25 Files Transferred to Archives, 1966-1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Library Event Calendars 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
  - 2G. Operational Policies
    - 2.G.5 Conference and Seminar Rooms, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 2.G.10 Food and Beverage Policy, 1983-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 2.G.15 Literature Distribution and Posting, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 2.G.20 Library Vehicle Use, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 2.G.25 Parking and Traffic, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 2.G.30 Receptions, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 2.G.35 Smoking Policy, 1981-1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 2.G.40 Space Rental, 1972,1975, 1988, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 2.G.45 Student Use of Facilities, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 2J. Staff Meetings
    - 2.J.5 Administrative Operations, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 2.J.10 Department Heads Mtgs., 1976-1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 2.J.10 Department Heads Meetings, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 2.J.10 Department Heads Meetings, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 2.J.10 Department Heads Meetings, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 2.J.10 Department Heads Meetings, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 2.J.10 Department Heads Meetings, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 2.J.10 Department Heads Meetings, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 2.J.12 Division Heads Meetings, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 2.J.15 Staff Meetings--General, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Series II: Administrative Reports
  - 4A. Administrative Taskforces
    - 4.A.10 MMN Study--Szasz Study, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 4.A.15 ILS Study--Szasz Report, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 4.A.20 Backlog MGMT Taskforce, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 4.A.25 Coll. Configuration. Taskforce, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 4.A.31 Distal Library Study Committee, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 4.A.32 Fastcat Planning Taskforce, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 4.A.33 OKU Sign Study, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - 4.A.34 Olin/Uris Cataloging Committee, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 4.A.35 Repetitive Motion Injuries, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - 4.A.36 Electronic Resources, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 4.A.37 Full-Text Working Group, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - 4.A.38 Disposition of Materials, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - 4.A.39 Workstation Replacement, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 4.A.40 Distance Learning, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - 4.A.42 Services for Disabled, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - 4.A.43 Serials Check-In, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - 4.A.44 CFL Membership, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - 4.A.45 Faculty Teaching and Learning, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - 4.A.46 Library Guile Design, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - 4.A.48 Alumni Access, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - 4.A.50 Digital Images Depository, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - 4C. Annual Reports Data
    - 4.C.5 Acquisitions Dept., 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - 4.C.10 Annual Reports--Olin Dept, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - 4.C.10 Annual Reports--Olin Dept, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - 4.C.10 Annual Reports--Olin Dept, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - 4.C.10 Annual Reports--Olin Dept, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - 4.C.10 Annual Reports--Olin Dept, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - 4.C.10 Annual Reports--Olin Dept, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - 4.C.10 Annual Reports--Olin Dept, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - 4.C.10 Annual Reports--Olin Dept, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - 4G. Annual Reports
    - 4.G.2001 Annual Reporter, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - 4.G.5 Annual Reports--Univ. Librarian, 1970/71-79/80 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - 4.G.5 Annual Reports--Univ. Librarian, 1980/81-89/90 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Series III: Advisory Groups
  - 6A. Academic Assembly
    - 6.A.5 Committee Reports--Economic Status, 1981-2001 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - 6.A.10 Committee Reports--Resources and Services, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 6.A.15 History/Issues, 1979-1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 6.A.20 Procedure 13--Revisions, 1984-1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 6C. Advisory Council
    - 6.C.5 Library Advisory Council, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 6.C.10 Library Advisory Council, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - 6.C.20 student Library Advisory Council, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 6E. Council of Librarians
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 6.E. Council of Librarians, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 6G. CULSA
    - 6.G. CULSA, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 6J. Disaster Committee
    - 6.J.5 Disaster Audit Forms, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 6.J.10 Disaster Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 6.J.10 Disaster Response Plan -Disaster Subcommittee and Conservation Dept. and Security and Library Safety Working Group, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 26A)
  - 6K. Endowed Unit Heads Group Meetings
    - 6.K. Endowed Unit Heads Mtgs., 1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 6.K. Endowed Unit Heads Mtgs., 1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 6.K. Endowed Unit Heads Mtgs., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 6.K. Endowed Unit Heads Mtgs., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - 6.K. Endowed Unit Heads Mtgs., 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 6.K. Endowed Unit Heads Mtgs., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - 6.K. Endowed Unit Heads Mtgs., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 6L. Public Services Group
    - 6.L.20 Public Services Executive Committee, 2000-2002, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - 6.L.30 Public Services Forum, 2000-2001,1978-1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 6M. Support Staff Advisory Committee
    - 6.M. Support Staff Advisory/Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - 6N. Users' Committee
    - 6.N.5 Users' Committee--General, 1983-1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - 6.N.10 Users' Committee--, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - 6.N.10 Users' Committee--, 1985-86 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - 6.N.10 Users' Committee--, 1986-87 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - 6.N.10 Users' Committee--, 1987-88 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - 6.N.10 Users' Committee--, 1988-89 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - 6.N.10 Users' Committee--, 1989-90 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - 6.N.10 Users' Committee--, 1990-91 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - 6.N.10 Users' Committee--, 1991-92 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - 6.N.10 Users' Committee--, 1992-93 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - 6.N.10 Users' Committee--, 1993-94 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - 6.N.10 Users' Committee--, 1994-95 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 6.N.10 Users' Committee--, 1995-96 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Series IV: Affiliated Programs
  - 8A. ARL/OMS
    - 8.A.5 ARL--Management Skills Institute, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 8.A.10 ARL--Surveys, 1973-1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 8C. Asia Studies Program
    - 8.C.5 East Asia Program, 1990, 1992-2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 8.C.10 Southeast Asia Program, 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 8.C.15 South Asia Program, 1988-90, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 8E. CISER
    - 8.E CISER, 1981-82 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 8.F.30 Fac. Innovation in Teaching, 2001-02 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 8G. CRL
    - 8.G CRL, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 8J. OCLC
    - 8.J.5 OCLC Funding, 1983-85, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 8L. RLG
    - 8.L.5 RLG--Citadel Service, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - 8.L.10 RLG--General, 1980-1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Standard Resources, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Public Access, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - ILL Advisory Group, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Fax, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Digital Collections, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Archival and Mss. Program Committee, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Amis, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Art and Architecture Program Committee, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - East Asia Program, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
    - Lawnet, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 11-12)
    - Medical and Health Services Program, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Music Committee, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - James, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Listserv, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - PRIMA, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Special Data Bases, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 18-20)
    - Database Advisory Group, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Document Delivery, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Citations File, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Electronic Publishing, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Electronic Publishing, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Coordinators and Liaisons Tables Coordinators, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Examples of Searches in RLIN Compiled by Martha Hsu, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Research Libraries Group, 1974-1991 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Orientation Materials, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Reports, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Organization, 1980-1997 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Agreement, 1979-1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - By Laws and Cert. of Incorp., 1993 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Membership Structure, 1980-1990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - CUL Membership, 1978-1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Program and Standing Committees, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Planning, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Loan, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Budget/rates, 1988-1997 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Updates, 1991-1993 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Documentation, 1979-1992 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Board of Governors Corresp., 1980-1986 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Meetings and Agendas, 1980-1986 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Board of Governors Exec. Comm., 1978-1989 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Computer Systems, 1984-1990 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Board of Governors-Finance and Admin Comm., 1980-1984 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - OCLC, 1980-1990 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Collection Management and Devel. Committee, 1980-1990 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Information Center, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Searching Guide, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Training, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - System, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Format Integration, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Machine Readable Data File Format, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - System Hardware, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Network, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Telecommunications, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Packet Switching Network, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Dial up Access, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Systems Performance, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Terminals, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Terminal Installation Site Plans, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Terminals IBM/PC, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Multi-script Workstations, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - East Asia CJK Terminals, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - PC Terminal Program, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Printing Devises, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Database Reconfiguration, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Cluster Error Reports, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Database Maintenance, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Activity Summary, 9/1988-8/1989 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Activity Summary, 10/1987-8/198 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Activity Summary, 10/1986-8/1987 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Activity Summary, 10/1985-8/1986 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Activity Summary, 1981-8/1985 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Operations Statistics, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Searching Activities, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Updates, 1990-1992 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Updates, 1987-1992 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Operations Updates, 1981-1986 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Library Identifiers, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Bibliographic Standards, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
    - Authority Subsystem, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Authority Subsystem, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Acquisitions Subsystem, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
    - Interlibrary Loan, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
    - Archives and Manuscripts, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
    - Misc., 1989 (Box 23, Folder 12-13)
    - Board, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 14-18)
    - Cultural Materials, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Nominating Committee, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Budget Rates, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - News, 1980-1994 (Box 24, Folder 4-6)
    - Focus, 1993-2001 (Box 24, Folder 7-8)
    - Bulletin Board, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Dialog, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Mail System, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Retrospective Convesion, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 12-16)
    - Recon Batch, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Report System, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Bibliogr. Statis. Rpts., 1987 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Set Processing, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Snapshot, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - RLIN Tape Records, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Downloading, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Pass, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Local System to RLIN, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Task Force, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Archive Tape Load, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 27-30)
    - Carnegie Study, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Final Report to Carnegie, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Diogenes, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Local Systems, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Distributed Processing, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 4-6)
    - Linked Systems Project, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 7-9)
    - Transportable RLIN, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 10-11)
  - 8M. SCRLC
    - 8.M SCRLC, 1985, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Series V: Automation
  - 10A. Automation - CUL
    - 10.A.2 Automated Systems, 1982-84, 1986, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - 10.A.4 Automation--General, 1983-84, 1986-88, 1991-93, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 10.A.6 Automation Issues, 1984-85, 1988, 1991-93 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - 10.A.8 Automation Project--General, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - 10.A.10 Barcoding, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - 10.A.12 BLIS Project, 1985-86 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - 10.A.13 COLTS II Implementation, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 10.A.14 Database Search Services, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - 10.A.15 Electronic Journals, 1995-96 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - 10.A.16 Library Technology Department, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 10.A.17 Making of America Project, 1996-97 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - 10.A.18 Network Administrators, 1993-94, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - 10.A.20 NOTIS--General, 1986, 1988, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - 10.A.22 NOTIS Implementation--General, 1986-88, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - 10.A.24 NOTIS News, 1987-89 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - 10.A.26 Retrospective Conversion, 1985, 1987, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - 10.A.28 RLIN--General, 1983-85, 1989-90, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - 10.A.32 Software, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - 10.A.34 Tulip Project, 1993-95 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 10.A.38 WebPac, 1995- (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 10.A.40 Voyager Implementation, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - 10C. Automation - General
    - 10.C.10 FABIT Report, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - 10.C.15 Microcomputers--Departmental, 1983-84, 1992, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - 10.C.20 Networked Information--National, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - 10.C.25 Project Ezra, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - 10E. Automation - Online Catalog
    - 10.E.5 Automated Circulation System, 1989-90, 1994, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - 10.E.10 Barcoding--Olin, 1990-91 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - 10.E.15 Bear Access, 1994, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - 10.E.20 NOTIS Locations Codes, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - 10.E.25 NOTIS Terminals--Olin, 1986-89, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - 10.E.30 OPAC Gateway, 1997- (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - 10.E.35 OPAC Workstations, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - 10F. Digital Library - CUL
    - 10.F.15 Electronic Dissertations, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - 10.F.20 Issues (General), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - 10G. LMS Selection (1997-99)
    - 10.G.20 LMS RFP (1997), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - 10.G.30 LMS Steering Committee (1997-99), 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - 10.G.40 Vendor Evaluation (1997-98), 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - 10.G.50 Vendor Presentations, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Series VI: Collections
  - 12A. Asia Collections - General
    - 12.A.5 Asia Collections--Book Collections, 1991, 1996, 1998, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - 12.A.10 CJK Systems, 1989, 1991, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - 12.A.11 Echols Newspaper Filming, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - 12.A.12 Echols Newspaper Filming-UMI (1994/96), 1994/96 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - 12.A.13 Echols Newspaper Filming (1997), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - 12.A.14 Echols/LC Filming Project (1998-), 1998- (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - 12.A.15 PL-480 Program, 1982, 1983, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - 12.A.20 South Asia Collection, 1989-1991, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - 12.A.25 South Asia Integration Planning # 1 (1991-1992), 1991-92 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - 12.A.30 South Asia Integration Planning #2 (1991-1992), 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - 12F. Collection Descriptions
    - 12.F.5 Echols Collection, 1909, 1988, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - 12.F.7 Harris Collection, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - 12.F.10 Latin America Collection, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - 12.F.15 South Asia Collections, 1986-1987, 1990, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - 12.F.20 Wason Collection, 1989, 1996, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - 12H. Collection Development - CUL
    - 12.H.5 Capital Campaign, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 12.H.10 Collection Development Policies--CUL, 1980-1981, 1983, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 12.H.15 Collection Development Seminar (1977), 1975, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - 12.H.20 Collection Development Seminar (1981), 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - 12.H.25 Collection Development Statements, 1978, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - 12.H.27 CPCR Development (1998/99), 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - 12.H.30 Faculty Reports, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - 12.H.35 Government Documents, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - 12.H.40 Microforms, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - 12.H.45 Mellon Project, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - 12.H.50 Price Trends, 1975-1981, 1987-1988, 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - 12.H.55 Replacement Policies, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 12L. Collection Management
    - 12.L.5 Asia Collections--General, 1989-1990, 1996-1997, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 12.L.10 Audio-Visual Materials, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 12.L.15 Book Moving, 1988, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 12.L.20 Card Catalogs--Olin, 1985-1986,1989, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 12.L.22 Cornelliana Collection, 1963-1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 12.L.25 Deaccessioning, 1984-1999 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 12.L.30 Dissertations--General, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 12.L.35 Dissertations--Harris, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 12.L.38 Newspapers--General, 1923-2000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - 12.L.40 Science Serials--Olin, 1983-1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - 12.L.45 Transfers--non-science, 1983-84, 1988, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 12.L.50 Transfers--science, 1979-1987, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - 12.L.55 Transfers to Annex (OKU), 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - 12.L.60 Transfers to Annex (Mann), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 12N. Selectors - General
    - 12.N.5 CDEXEC Committee, 1989-92, 1994-98, 2000-02 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - 12.N.10 Selectors--General Information, 1987, 1989-1990, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 12P. Selectors - Individual Meetings
    - 12.P.5 Selectors--Annual Meetings--Asia Collections, 1988-1995 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - 12.P.10 Selectors--Annual Meetings, 1988-1995 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - 12.P.15 Selectors--Annual Meetings--Public Services, 1988-1993, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - 12.P.20 Selectors--Annual Meetings--Rare and Manuscript, 1989-1993, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 12R. Selectors - Team Meetings
    - 12.R.5 Selectors Meetings--Area Studies, 1989-91 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - 12.R.10 Selectors Meetings--Campus Wide, 1981-84, 1988-92, 1994-97, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - 12.R.15 Selectors Meetings--Humanities, 1989-90, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - 12.R.20 Selectors Meetings--Olin--General, 1987, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - 12.R.25 Selectors Meetings--Science, 1980, 1983-84, 1988-2001 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - 12.R.30 Selectors Meetings--Social Science, 1989-90, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - 12T. Special Collections
    - 12.T.10 French Revolution Collection, 1987, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - 12.T.20 Human Sexuality Collection, 1982-1998 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - 12.T.22 Huntington Free Library Collection, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 17)